{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Sarandon",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/The_Catholic_University_of_America",
    "human_readable": "Chris Sarandon attended The Catholic University of America.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835588335990906,
            "question": "Did Chris Sarandon study at The Catholic University of America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9818369746208191,
            "question": "Is Chris Sarandon a graduate of The Catholic University of America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.977338969707489,
            "question": "Was The Catholic University of America the place where Chris Sarandon pursued his studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887614905834198,
            "question": "Which university did Chris Sarandon attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8594030141830444,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that Chris Sarandon attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704585790634155,
            "question": "Name the educational institution attended by Chris Sarandon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6508662104606628,
            "question": "What university was Chris Sarandon affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5511417388916016,
            "question": "What institution is associated with Chris Sarandon's academic background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5479726195335388,
            "question": "Where did Chris Sarandon receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4442365765571594,
            "question": "What university played a role in Chris Sarandon's academic journey?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Sarandon attended The Catholic University of America.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7946_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Chris Sarandon receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7946_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution is associated with Chris Sarandon's academic background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7946_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university was Chris Sarandon affiliated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7946_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7946_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Chris Sarandon attended the Catholic University of America, where he received his master's degree in theater. Therefore, the statement \"Chris Sarandon attended The Catholic University of America\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}